Glory, glory, power!
Hallelujah!
We want to tell the viewers all over the world,
I mean those who are under the influence of our voice,
we know your desire and your determination.
Jesus loves you.
We salute your time.
We Christians, our time is our faith.
Tell your neighbour, 'My time is my faith'.
'My faith is my time'.
Viewers, with God, all things are possible.
We know there are many viewers that are on the sickbed.
They have been with us since morning while they are lying on the sickbed.
I want to tell you, it is time to receive.
Distance is not a barrier.
Whatever condition, whatever situation you are in,
whatever name they call it -
never a sickness Jesus cannot heal,
never a burden Jesus cannot bear
and never a problem Jesus cannot solve.
Right now, be with me; I am with you.
This is a question of the heart.
Heart-to-heart.
Let someone say, 'Heart-to-heart'.
Because faith is of man's heart.
Your 'Amen' may not come from your heart, your attention may not come from your heart
but I'm telling you, this is a question of the heart.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, whatever means satan might have used to cage you...
There are many means satan can use to cage one -
affliction, setback, depression, rejection.
Whatever means satan might have used to cage you,
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Listen, with God all things are possible.
Whatever means satan might have used to cage you, you are released, in the name of Jesus!
Be it affliction - you are released, in the name of Jesus!
You are delivered, in the name of Jesus!
You are healed, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
There are many people that are in a cage.
You will see them moving, but they are in a cage.
It is not only those who are in the prison that are in a cage.
The most serious cage is for one to be moving around and yet, he is in a cage.
Whatever cage, whatever means satan might have used to cage you,
be released, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to release yourself, in the mighty name of Jesus!
Begin to release yourself.
I release myself, in the name of Jesus!
I release myself, in the mighty name of Jesus!
I'm released! Begin to release yourself!
Cage of affliction! Cage of setback! Cage of limitation! Cage of disappointment!
Cage of disappointment!
Cage of rejection!
Cage of affliction!
Cage of hatred!
Cage of setback!
Cage of disappointment!
Begin to release yourself.
Release yourself, in the name of Jesus!
Jesus is involved; it is time.
Be free!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You are released!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
The blood of Jesus sets me free from sin and sorrow.
The blood of Jesus sets me free.
In Jesus Christ's name!
Every damaged organ, begin to function, in the name of Jesus!
Every damaged organ, be it in your kidney, be it in your liver, in your tendons, in your fluids,
in your bones, in your blood, begin to function!
Begin to function.
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Begin to function right now.
Every organ in your system - be it your liver, be it your kidney -
every organ, be it your liver, be it your kidney, every organ, begin to function!
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Begin to function.
Pray Along With Prophet T. B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
There is power there is power
There is power in the blood
There is deliverance there is deliverance
There is deliverance in the blood
There is healing there is healing
There is healing in the blood
There is prosperity there is prosperity
There is prosperity in the blood
There is freedom there is freedom
There is freedom in the blood
Begin to receive, in the name of Jesus!
Receive your freedom, in the name of Jesus!
I command healing on you.
I command deliverance on you.
Receive!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Right now, begin to change your words and your thoughts.
I am healed!
I am delivered!
I am blessed!
I am free!
Begin to confess your freedom right now. Confess your freedom.
Confess your freedom.
Breakthrough!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Listen - in your heart, I can hear breakthrough.
In your business, breakthrough.
In your career, breakthrough.
In your health, breakthrough.
In your life, breakthrough.
In your destiny, breakthrough.
Breakthrough!
In Jesus' name!
I can't wait to hear your testimony!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name